A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 1997-2006 [bulk 2002-2005]
Library of Virginia
- Series IV: Correspondence with State Agencies, 1997-2005 [bulk 2002-2005]
  - Health: Constitutent Issues, 1999-2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Health: Constituent Issues, 1999-2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Health: Contracts, 2001-2004 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Health: Decision Memos, 2002-2005 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Health: Delegate Welch, 2004 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Health: Drought, 2002 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Health: Emergency Organizations, 2003-2005 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Health: Emergency Preparedness, 2004 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Health: EPA Consolidated Certification and Assurance Program, 2004 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Health: Farm Products, 2005 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Health: FOIA Requests, 2003 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Health: General Information, 2001-2005, fo. 1 of 4 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Health: General Information, 2001-2005, fo. 2 of 4 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Health: General Information, 2001-2005, fo. 3 of 4 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Health: General Information, 2001-2005, fo. 4 of 4 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Health: Grants, 2002-2005, fo. 1 of 4 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Health: Grants, 2002-2005, fo. 2 of 4 (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Health: Grants, 2002-2005, fo. 3 of 4 (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - Health: Grants, 2002-2005, fo. 4 of 4 (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - Health: Grants, 2004-2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - Health: Grants, 2004-2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - Health: Health Professional Shortage Areas, 2003-2005 (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - Health: Influenza Vaccination Campaign, 2003-2004 (Box 82, Folder 24)
  - Health: JLARC, 2003 (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - Health: Joint Commission on Healthcare, 2002-2005 (Box 82, Folder 26)
  - Health: Legislative Contact, 2002-2003 (Box 82, Folder 27)
  - Health: Legislative Issues, 2001-2005 (Box 82, Folder 28)
  - Health: Management Scorecard, 2004 (Box 82, Folder 29)
  - Health: Mandates, 2002-2004 (Box 82, Folder 30)
  - Health: Master Settlement Agreement, 2002 (Box 82, Folder 31)
  - Health: Media Issues, 2002-2003, fo. 1 of 3 (Box 82, Folder 32)
  - Health: Media Issues, 2002-2003, fo. 2 of 3 (Box 82, Folder 33)
  - Health: Media Issues, 2002-2003, fo. 3 of 3 (Box 82, Folder 34)
  - Health: Media Issues, 2004 (Box 82, Folder 35)
  - Health: Miscellaneous, 2001-2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - Health: Miscellaneous, 2001-2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - Health: National Stockpile, 2004 (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - Health: Nursing Home Survey Reports, 2004 (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - Health: Our Health - Proposed Funding Request, 2004 (Box 83, Folder 24)
  - Health: Patrick County Memorial Hospital, undated (Box 83, Folder 25)
  - Health: Personnel, 2005 (Box 83, Folder 26)
  - Health: Policy Issues, 2002-2004 (Box 83, Folder 27)
  - Health: Preparedness / Terrorism, 2001-2002 (Box 83, Folder 28)
  - Health: Preparedness / Terrorism, 2001-2002 (Box 83, Folder 28)
  - Health: Prescription Drug Programs, 2001-2004 (Box 83, Folder 29)
  - Health: Public / Private Programs to Improve Health Care Access in Rural Virginia, 2003 (Box 83, Folder 30)
  - Health: Public Awareness Campaign, 2003 (Box 83, Folder 31)
  - Health: Regulations, 2002-2005 (Box 83, Folder 32)
  - Health: Requests for Proclamations, 2002-2003 (Box 83, Folder 33)
  - Health: Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, 2004 (Box 83, Folder 34)
  - Health: Rural Obstetrical Care Group, 2004 (Box 83, Folder 35)
  - Health: Safe Drinking Water, 2003-2005 (Box 83, Folder 36)
  - Health: Septic System, 2004 (Box 83, Folder 37)
  - Health: Severe Accute Respiratory Syndrome (SARS), 2003 (Box 83, Folder 38)
  - Health: Soil Evaluations, 2001-2002 (Box 83, Folder 39)
  - Health: Special Requests from the Governor, undated (Box 83, Folder 40)
  - Health: Suicide Prevention, 2002-2003 (Box 83, Folder 41)
  - Health: Surveys, 2002-2003, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 83, Folder 42)
  - Health: Surveys, 2002-2003, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 83, Folder 43)
  - Health: Technology Issues, 2003-2004 (Box 83, Folder 44)
  - Health: Temporary Assistance to Needy Families (TANF), 2004 (Box 83, Folder 45)
  - Health: Uninsured Medical Catastrophe Fund, 2001 (Box 83, Folder 46)
  - Health: Virginia Aligned Against Sexual Assault, 2004 (Box 83, Folder 47)
  - Health: Virginia Center for Healthy Communities, 2001-2002 (Box 83, Folder 48)
  - Health: Virginia Resource Authority, 2004 (Box 83, Folder 49)
  - Health: Virginia Rural Health Resource Center, 2002-2003 (Box 83, Folder 50)
  - Health: Virginia Secure Panel, 2002-2003 (Box 83, Folder 51)
  - Health: Walk Smart Virginia, 2004 (Box 83, Folder 52)
  - Health: West Nile Virus, 2002 (Box 83, Folder 53)
  - Health: WIC, 2003-2005 (Box 83, Folder 54)
  - Health: Women's Health, 2001 (Box 83, Folder 55)
  - Health: Workforce Issues, 2002 (Box 83, Folder 56)
  - Health Professions: Board of Nursing / NCLEX test sites, 2005 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Health Professions: Boards, 2003-2005 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Health Professions: Constituent Issues, 2002 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Health Professions: Decision Memos, 2002-2004 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Health Professions: FOIA Requests, 2002 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Health Professions: General Information for Board Members, 2000, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Health Professions: General Information for Board Members, 2000, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Health Professions: General Information, 2003-2004 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Health Professions: HB1441 Guidelines, 2003 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Health Professions: Legislative Contact, 2002 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Health Professions: Miscellaneous, 2003-2005 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Health Professions: Nursing, 2002 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Health Professions: Personnel, 2002 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Health Professions: Physical Therapists, 2002 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Health Professions: Regulations, 2003 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Health Professions: Special Requests from Governor, undated (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Health Professions: Studies 2002 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Health Professions: Technology Issues, 2003 (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - Health Professions, Weekly Reports 2002 (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - Inspector General: General Information, 2003-2004 (Box 83, Folder 57)
  - Inspector General: Inspection Reports, 2002-2005 (Box 83, Folder 58)
  - Inspector General: Legislative Issues, 2002 (Box 83, Folder 59)
  - Inspector General: Study Letter, 2002 (Box 83, Folder 60)
  - Medical Assistance Services: AIDS Waiver, 2002 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Medical Assistance Services: Budget Issues, 2002-2005 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Medical Assistance Services: Center for Medicare and Medicaid Services, 2005 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Medical Assistance Services: Constitutent Issues, 2002-2005 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Medical Assistance Services: Crossover Claims, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Medical Assistance Services: DD Waivers, 2002-2004 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Medical Assistance Services: Decision Memos, 2002-2005 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Medical Assistance Services: Dental, 2002-2004 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Medical Assistance Services: Drug Discount Card Program, 2004 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Medical Assistance Services: Dyntek, 2002-2003 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Medical Assistance Services: Fair Rental Value, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Medical Assistance Services: FAMIS, 2001-2004, fo. 1 of 7 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Medical Assistance Services: FAMIS, 2001-2004, fo. 2 of 7 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Medical Assistance Services: FAMIS, 2001-2004, fo. 3 of 7 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - Medical Assistance Services: FAMIS, 2001-2004, fo. 4 of 7 (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Medical Assistance Services: FAMIS, 2001-2004, fo. 5 of 7 (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - Medical Assistance Services: FAMIS, 2001-2004, fo. 6 of 7 (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - Medical Assistance Services: FAMIS, 2001-2004, fo. 7 of 7 (Box 84, Folder 18)
  - Medical Assistance Services: FOIA Requests, 2002 (Box 84, Folder 19)
  - Medical Assistance Services: General Information, 2002-2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 84, Folder 20)
  - Medical Assistance Services: General Information, 2002-2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 84, Folder 21)
  - Medical Assistance Services: Grants, 2002 (Box 84, Folder 22)
  - Medical Assistance Services: HIPPA, 2005 (Box 84, Folder 23)
  - Medical Assistance Services: Hot Button Issues, 2002-2005 (Box 84, Folder 24)
  - Medical Assistance Services: Interagency Agreement, 2004 (Box 84, Folder 25)
  - Medical Assistance Services: Issue Briefs, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 26)
  - Medical Assistance Services: JLARC Studies, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 27)
  - Medical Assistance Services: Lag Pay, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 28)
  - Medical Assistance Services: Legislative Issues, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 29)
  - Medical Assistance Services: Long Term Care, 2000-2001 (Box 84, Folder 30)
  - Medical Assistance Services: Media Issues, 2002-2003 (Box 84, Folder 31)
  - Medical Assistance Services: Medicaid Disallowance, 2001 (Box 84, Folder 32)
  - Medical Assistance Services: Medicaid Managed Care, 2002-2005 (Box 84, Folder 33)
  - Medical Assistance Services: Miscellaneous, 2004-2005 (Box 84, Folder 34)
  - Medical Assistance Services: MMIS, 2003-2004 (Box 84, Folder 35)
  - Medical Assistance Services: New Medicaid Management Information System (MMIS), 2002, fo. 1 of 5 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Medical Assistance Services: New Medicaid Management Information System (MMIS), 2002, fo. 2 of 5 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Medical Assistance Services: New Medicaid Management Information System (MMIS), 2002, fo. 3 of 5 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Medical Assistance Services: New Medicaid Management Information System (MMIS), 2002, fo. 4 of 5 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Medical Assistance Services: New Medicaid Management Information System (MMIS), 2002, fo. 5 of 5 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Medical Assistance Services: Personnel (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Medical Assistance Services: Pharmacy and Therapeutics Committee, 2003-2004 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Medical Assistance Services: Preferred Drug List, 2003-2004 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Medical Assistance Services: Prescription Drug Program, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Medical Assistance Services: Program for all inclusive care of elderly, 2004-2005 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Medical Assistance Services: Regulations, 2002 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Medical Assistance Services: Report on Audit, 2004-2005 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Medical Assistance Services: Revenue Maximization, 2001 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Medical Assistance Services: Robert E. Rose Memorial, 2003 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Medical Assistance Services: Share Card, undated (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Medical Assistance Services: State Plan Amendment, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Medical Assistance Services: Technology Issues, 2001-2004 (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - Medical Assistance Services: Transportation Issues, 2002-2004 (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - Mental Health: Business Plan - Small Business and Minority-Owned Businesses, 2002 (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - Mental Health: Executive Orders 61 and 84 (2004-2005), 2004-2005, fo. 1 of 5 (Box 85, Folder 20)
  - Mental Health: Executive Orders 61 and 84 (2004-2005), 2004-2005, fo. 2 of 5 (Box 85, Folder 21)
  - Mental Health: Executive Orders 61 and 84 (2004-2005), 2004-2005, fo. 3 of 5 (Box 85, Folder 22)
  - Mental Health: Executive Orders 61 and 84 (2004-2005), 2004-2005, fo. 4 of 5 (Box 85, Folder 23)
  - Mental Health: Executive Orders 61 and 84 (2004-2005), 2004-2005, fo. 5 of 5 (Box 85, Folder 24)
  - Mental Health: Grants, 2002-2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 85, Folder 25)
  - Mental Health: Grants, 2002-2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 85, Folder 26)
  - Mental Health: IDEA Funding, 2005 (Box 85, Folder 27)
  - Mental Health: Kovar Summer Institute 2004 Final Report, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 28)
  - Mental Health: Legislative Issues, 2002-2003 (Box 85, Folder 29)
  - Mental Health: Mandate Assessment, 2005 (Box 85, Folder 30)
  - Mental Health: Media Issues, 2002-2003 (Box 85, Folder 31)
  - Mental Health: Miscellaneous, 2002-2003 (Box 85, Folder 32)
  - Mental Health: Olmstead Task Force, 2002-2003, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 85, Folder 33)
  - Mental Health: Olmstead Task Force, 2002-2003, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 85, Folder 34)
  - Mental Health: Personnel, 2003-2004 (Box 85, Folder 35)
  - Mental Health: Policy Issues, 2003-2004 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Mental Health: Project to Assist in Transition from Homelessness, 2004 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Mental Health: Regulations, 2002 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Mental Health: Regulations, 2002 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Mental Health: Safe Families in Recovery Project, 2004 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Mental Health: Sexually Violent Preditor Program, 2004 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Mental Health: Sixth Quarterly Report, 2003-2004 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Mental Health: SJR 97 / HJR 142, 2002 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Mental Health: Southwest Virginia Mental Health Institute, 2003 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Mental Health: Special Request from the Governor, 2003 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Mental Health: State Facilities, 2002-2004 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Mental Health: Studies, 2002-2004, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Mental Health: Studies, 2002-2004, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Mental Health: Substance Abuse Prevention, 1999-2003 (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Mental Health: Substance Abuse Services Council, 2003-2004 (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Mental Health: Substance Abuse Treatment for Inmates, 2004 (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - Mental Health: Synar Annual Report for FY 2004, 2003-2004 (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - Mental Health: Technologies Issues, 2002-2005 (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - Mental Health: Virginia Institute of Psychiatry and Mental Health, 2002 (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - Mental Health: Virginia Office for Protection and Advocacy, 2004 (Box 86, Folder 20)
  - Mental Health: Workforce Issues, 2002 (Box 86, Folder 21)
  - Photographs (Box 86, Folder 22)
  - Rehabilitative Services: Annual Reports, 2003 (Box 86, Folder 23)
  - REVIEW: Rehabilitative Services: Appeal, 2005, fo. 1 of 3 (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - REVIEW: Rehabilitative Services: Appeal, 2005, fo. 2 of 3 (Box 160, Folder 2)
  - REVIEW: Rehabilitative Services: Appeal, 2005, fo. 3 of 3 (Box 160, Folder 3)
  - REVIEW: Rehabilitative Services: Appeal Hearings, 2004 (Box 160, Folder 4)
  - REVIEW: Rehabilitative Services: Appeals Hearing, 2002 [1] (Box 160, Folder 7)
  - REVIEW: Rehabilitative Services, 2002 [2] (Box 160, Folder 6)
  - REVIEW: Rehabilitative Services: Appeals Hearing, 2002 [3], fo. 1 of 2 (Box 160, Folder 7)
  - REVIEW: Rehabilitative Services: Appeals Hearing, 2002 [3], fo. 2 of 2 (Box 160, Folder 8)
  - REVIEW: Rehabilitative Services: Appeals Hearing, 2003 [1], fo. 1 of 2 (Box 160, Folder 9)
  - REVIEW: Rehabilitative Services: Appeals Hearing, 2003 [1], fo. 2 of 2 (Box 160, Folder 10)
  - REVIEW: Rehabilitative Services: Appeals Hearing, 2003 [2], fo. 1 of 2 (Box 160, Folder 11)
  - REVIEW: Rehabilitative Services: Appeals Hearing, 2003 [2], fo. 2 of 2 (Box 160, Folder 12)
  - REVIEW: Rehabilitative Services: Appeals Hearing, 2004 [1], fo. 1 of 2 (Box 160, Folder 13)
  - REVIEW: Rehabilitative Services: Appeals Hearing, 2004 [1], fo. 2 of 2 (Box 160, Folder 14)
  - REVIEW: Rehabilitative Services: Appeals Hearing, 2004 [2] (Box 160, Folder 15)
  - REVIEW: Rehabilitative Services: Appeals Hearing, 2004 [3] (Box 160, Folder 16)
  - Rehabilitative Services: Boards, 2002-2003 (Box 86, Folder 24)
  - Rehabilitative Services: Briefs, 2004 (Box 86, Folder 25)
  - Rehabilitative Services: Budget Issues, 2002 (Box 86, Folder 26)
  - REVIEW: Rehabilitative Services: Constitutent Correspondence, 2004 (Box 160, Folder 17)
  - Rehabilitative Services: Decision Memos, 2002-2005 (Box 86, Folder 27)
  - Rehabilitative Services: Disability Determination Services, 2004 (Box 86, Folder 28)
  - Rehabilitative Services: General Information, 2002-2005 (Box 86, Folder 29)
  - Rehabilitative Services: Grants, 2003 (Box 86, Folder 30)
  - Rehabilitative Services: Legislative Issues, 2002 (Box 86, Folder 31)
  - Rehabilitative Services: Policy Issues, 2001 (Box 86, Folder 32)
  - Rehabilitative Services: Prescription Drug Assistance Programs, undated (Box 86, Folder 33)
  - Rehabilitative Services: Real Estate, 2004 (Box 86, Folder 34)
  - Rehabilitative Services: Requests for Proclamations, 2002-2003 (Box 86, Folder 35)
  - Rehabilitative Services: Studies, 2002 (Box 86, Folder 36)
  - Rehabilitative Services: Technology Issues, 2002-2004 (Box 86, Folder 37)
  - Rehabilitative Services: Wilder Commission, 2002 (Box 86, Folder 38)
  - Rehabilitative Services: Workforce Issues, 2002 (Box 86, Folder 39)
  - Social Services: Accounts, 2001-2005 (Box 86, Folder 40)
  - Social Services: Adult Protective Services Program, 2002-2004 (Box 86, Folder 41)
  - Social Services: African American Male Issues, 1998 (Box 86, Folder 42)
  - Social Services: Attorney General Issues, 2002 (Box 86, Folder 43)
  - Social Services: Budget Issues, 2002-2003 (Box 86, Folder 44)
  - Social Services: Caring Communities, 2004 (Box 86, Folder 45)
  - REVIEW: Social Services: Case [1], 2002, fo. 1 of 4 (Box 160, Folder 18)
  - REVIEW: Social Services: Case [1], 2002, fo. 2 of 4 (Box 160, Folder 19)
  - REVIEW: Social Services: Case [1], 2002, fo. 3 of 4 (Box 160, Folder 20)
  - REVIEW: Social Services: Case [1], 2002, fo. 4 of 4 (Box 160, Folder 21)
  - Social Services: Child Abuse and Neglect, 2002-2004 (Box 86, Folder 46)
  - Social Services: Child and Family Services Review, 2003-2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 86, Folder 47)
  - Social Services: Child and Family Services Review, 2003-2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 86, Folder 48)
  - Social Services: Child Care, 2001-2004 (Box 86, Folder 49)
  - Social Services: Child Day Care, 2002 (Box 86, Folder 50)
  - Social Services: Child Passenger Restraint Workgroup, 2003 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Social Services: Child Support Guideline Review Panel, 2001-2002, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Social Services: Child Support Guideline Review Panel, 2001-2002, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Social Services: Child Support, 2002 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Social Services: Conflict of Interests Act, 2005 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Social Services: Conmfort Care Homes, 2003 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Social Services: Constituent Issues, 2002-2005 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Social Services: Decision Memos, 2002-2003, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Social Services: Decision Memos, 2002-2003, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Social Services: Domestic Violence, 2001-2002 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Social Services: Early Childhood Care and Education (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Social Services: Energy Assistance, 2005 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Social Services: Executive Order for Americorps, 2002 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Social Services: Faith-Based Initiatives, 2001-2004, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Social Services: Faith-Based Initiatives, 2001-2004, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Social Services: Family Financial Literacy, LLC, 2002 (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Social Services: General Information, 2002-2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - Social Services: General Information, 2002-2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - Social Services: Grants, 2002-2004 (Box 87, Folder 19)
  - Social Services: Head Start, 2002-2003 (Box 87, Folder 20)
  - Social Services: Healthy Families, 2001-2004 (Box 87, Folder 21)
  - Social Services: Homelessness Issues, 2002 (Box 87, Folder 22)
  - Social Services: Homosexual Adoption, 2000-2002 (Box 87, Folder 23)
  - Social Services: Hot Button Issues, 2003 (Box 87, Folder 24)
  - Social Services: Legislative Contact, 2002-2005 (Box 87, Folder 25)
  - Social Services: Legislative Issues, 2002 (Box 87, Folder 26)
  - REVIEW: Social Services: Legislative Issues, 2002 (Box 159, Folder 11)
  - Social Services: Legislative Studies, 2002-2004, fo. 1 of 3 (Box 87B, Folder 1)
  - Social Services: Legislative Studies, 2002-2004, fo. 2 of 3 (Box 87B, Folder 2)
  - Social Services: Legislative Studies, 2002-2004, fo. 3 of 3 (Box 87B, Folder 3)
  - Social Services: Licensing, 2002-2004 (Box 87, Folder 27)
  - Social Services: Life Journeys, Inc., undated (Box 87, Folder 28)
  - REVIEW: Social Services: Litigation, 2002-2005, fo. 1 of 3 (Box 160, Folder 22)
  - REVIEW: Social Services: Litigation, 2002-2005, fo. 2 of 3 (Box 160, Folder 23)
  - REVIEW: Social Services: Litigation, 2002-2005, fo. 3 of 3 (Box 160, Folder 24)
  - Social Services: Loudoun County CAA Designation, 2005 (Box 87, Folder 29)
  - Social Services: Low Income Tax Credit, 2002 (Box 87, Folder 30)
  - Social Services: Lynn House, 2004 (Box 87, Folder 31)
  - Social Services: Mandate Assessment, 2002-2005 (Box 87, Folder 32)
  - Social Services: Media Issues, 2002-2003 (Box 87, Folder 33)
  - Social Services: Miscellaneous, 2003 (Box 87, Folder 34)
  - Social Services: Perinatal Substance Abuse, 2003 (Box 87A, Folder 1)
  - Social Services: Policy Issues, 2001 (Box 87A, Folder 2)
  - Social Services: Prisoner Re-Entry, undated (Box 87A, Folder 3)
  - Social Services: Refugee Issues, 2002 (Box 87A, Folder 4)
  - Social Services: Regulations, 2002-2005 (Box 87A, Folder 5)
  - Social Services: Reports, 2002-2005 (Box 87A, Folder 6)
  - Social Services: Request for Proclamations, 2002-2005 (Box 87A, Folder 7)
  - Social Services: Secretary's Triennial Child Support Guideline Review Panel Report, 2002 (Box 87A, Folder 8)
  - Social Services: State Emergency Response Team, 2004 (Box 87A, Folder 9)
  - Social Services: Technology Issues, 2004 (Box 87A, Folder 10)
  - Social Services: Temporary Assistance for Needy Families, 2001-2005, fo. 1 of 4 (Box 87A, Folder 11)
  - Social Services: Temporary Assistance for Needy Families, 2001-2005, fo. 2 of 4 (Box 87A, Folder 12)
  - Social Services: Temporary Assistance for Needy Families, 2001-2005, fo. 3 of 4 (Box 87A, Folder 13)
  - Social Services: Temporary Assistance for Needy Families, 2001-2005, fo. 4 of 4 (Box 87A, Folder 14)
  - Social Services: Uniform Assessment Instrument, 2005 (Box 87A, Folder 15)
  - Social Services: Women, Infants and Children (WIC), 2003 (Box 87A, Folder 16)
  - Social Services: Workforce Issues, 2002 (Box 87A, Folder 17)
  - Tobacco Settlement Foundation: General Information, undated (Box 87A, Folder 18)
  - Tobacco Settlement Foundation: Personnel, 2002 (Box 87A, Folder 19)
  - Tobacco Settlement Foundation: Survey, 2002 (Box 87A, Folder 20)
- Series V: Legislative Files, 2002-2005
  - 12 VAC 5-381 VDH, 2004-2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - 12 VAC 5-381 VDH, 2002-2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - 12 VAC 5-390-1 VDH, 2004-2005 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - 12 VAC 5-410 VDH, 2004-2005 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - 12 VAC 5-480 VDH, 2005 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - 12 VAC 5-500 VDH, 2003-2004 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - 12 VAC 5-507 VDH, 2002 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - 12 VAC 5-550 VDH, 2002-2003 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - 12 VAC 5-585 VDH, 2003-2005 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - 12 VAC 5-590 VDH, 2004-2005 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - 12 VAC 5-600 VDH, 2005 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - 12 VAC 5-615 VDH, 2002 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Amendment 04-09, 2004 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - 12 VAC 30-10 DMAS, 2003-2004 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - 12 VAC 5-586 VDH, 2003 (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - 12 VAC 30-10-150 DMAS, 2005 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - 12 VAC 30-40 DMAS, 2003-2005 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - 12 VAC 30-50 DMAS, 2003-2005, fo. 1 of 2 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - 12 VAC 30-50 DMAS, 2003-2005, fo. 2 of 2 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - 12 VAC 30-60 DMAS, 2005 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - 12 VAC 30-70 DMAS, 2003-2005 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - 12 VAC 30-80 DMAS, 2003-2005 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - 12 VAC 30-90 DMAS, 2003-2005 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - 12 VAC 30-70, 80 and 90 DMAS, 2005 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - 12 VAC 30-100 DMAS, 2002 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - 12 VAC 30-110 DMAS, 2002-2003 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - 12 VAC 30-120 DMAS, 2002-2005, fo. 1 of 3 (Box 90, Folder 2)